inwolton.com 2010-06-12

# INWOLTON.COM - SITE

This policy describes the ways we collect, store, use and protect your personal information. You accepted this policy when you signed up for our Service. We may amend this policy at any time by posting a revised version on our website. Any amendment or update to this policy nullifies the previous policy. If you use the Company’s services after such notification of changes in this policy, you will be bound by all such changes. At the time of such modification, you will have the opportunity to reject such modification by closure of your account.

**How we collect information about you**

When you visit our website, we collect your IP address and standard web log information, such as your browser type and the pages you accessed on our website.

If you open an account, we collect the following types of information from you:

Contact information - your name, address, phone, email, and other similar information.

Financial information – e-currency account numbers.

When you are using our Service, we collect information about your account transactions and we may collect information about your computer or other access device for fraud prevention purposes.

We may collect additional information from or about you in other ways not specifically described here. For example, we may collect information related to your contact with our customer support team or store results when you respond to a survey.

**How we protect and store personal information**

Throughout this policy, we use the term "personal information" to describe information that can be associated with a specific person and can be used to identify that person.

We store and process your personal information on our computers, and we protect it by maintaining physical, electronic and procedural safeguards. We use computer safeguards such as firewalls and data encryption, we enforce physical access controls to our buildings and files, and we authorize access to personal information only for those employees who require it to fulfill their job responsibilities.

**How we use the personal information we collect**

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a secure, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. We may use your personal information to:

provide the services and customer support you request;

process transactions and send notices about your transactions

resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;

prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms of Service;

customize, measure, and improve our services and the content and layout of our website;

send you targeted marketing, service update notices, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences;

compare information for accuracy and verify it with third parties.

**How we share personal information with other parties**

We may share your personal information with:

Law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties when

we are compelled to do so by a court order or similar legal procedure

we need to do so to comply with law

we believe in good faith that the disclosure of personal information is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity, or to investigate violations of our Terms of Service.

Inwolton will not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes and only shares your personal information with third parties as described in this policy.

**How you can access or change your personal information**

You can review and edit your personal information at any time by logging in to your account and clicking the Settings.
